# Vanja Paunovic

# Software Engineer

Belgrade, Serbia (+381) 65 541 9360 vana997@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/vpaunovic qithub.com/dzimiks

# **Summary**

I am a passionate, self-motivated and committed computer science student. The majority of my spare time I've spent on learning new algorithms and data structures. I have worked and thrived in a team setting through the internships I have had in the last two years. Learning from my teammates and constantly interacting with clients taught me discipline and it's giving me motivation to progress.

### **Work History**

Startup

July, 2017 - September, 2017

Full Stack Engineer

Developed MEAN stack web applications.

Created administrator management system for on-site content upload.

Designed and implemented web pages.

**Devana Technologies** 

July, 2016 - September, 2016

Frontend Developer Internship

Worked in small and efficient team.

#### Education

Bachelor in Computer Science
Union University, Faculty of Computing

2016 - present

High School Diploma XIV Belgrade Gymnasium 2012 - 2016

## **Projects**

**GeKoSeM** - Generic document manager. It can be used for organizing and editing documents with textual or graphical editor.

**Universal Installer** - Universal Installer is app that simulates installation process. It was a college project for Software Design course.

**TetrisAI** - TetrisAI represents basic Tetris simulation. It was my seminary project for Intelligent systems course.

PanRock Global - Designed complete website and implemented many functionalities.

FEFA - Maintained website and implemented news feed.

#### Languages

English - Professional working proficiency

Serbian - Native or bilingual proficiency

German - Elementary proficiency (Deutsches Sprachdiplom der Kultusministerkonferenz - A2)

# **Skills**

Java

C/C++

Python

HTML 5

CSS 3

Javascript

# **Honors And Awards**

#### CodeGovernment, May 2018 (3rd place)

Developed web app with simple UX design and smart search engine which simplifies usage of eGovernment portal.

#### MatHack, May 2018 (finalist)

Made web app that generates optimal trajectory from starting to ending point on map using machine learning algorithms.

#### FON Hackathon, April 2018 (1st place)

Developed web application using Big Data. The application goal is to provide data analysis for Telekom Serbia. Solution was distributed cloud-based analysis system and it has interactive data visualization. The system contains a tool for personalized package recommendation, as well as a tool for detecting irregularities of the network in real time.